MARCELO ANDRES PEREZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

mandresperez.uk@gmail.com | Denver, CO | (323) 371-7601 linkedin.com/in/marcelo-perez-7728b910a | github.com/mandresp

Profile Summary

Recently graduated Full Stack Developer with over five years Marketing and Real Estate work experience. Adaptive – Multi-cultural having lived in the US, Hong Kong and London. Fluent in written and spoken Mandarin and conversationally fluent in Cantonese. Creative – Skilled in Art/Design/Music.

Technical Skills

HTML | CSS | Javascript | JQuery | GraphQL | MERN Stack | Python | Bootstrap | Adobe Creative Suite | Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint) | Salesforce | MLS | CoStar | Pardot | Constant Contact | Landvision

Education

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP - ONLINE CERTIFICATE

- Gained hands-on experience and technical understanding of MERN stack & Bootstrap.
- Generated new code for three agile projects, Git-based source control, and Heroku-based deployment.
- Notable Projects:
 - o HOWDYNEIGHBOR Deployed Site: HOWDYNEIGHBOR Repository: GitHub
 - Utilized React to construct an application to help people find help in their community linked to a MongoDB database.
 - Constructed all page routes and assisted in the front end design of the site.
 - Key Tools: React, MongoDB, Nodejs, Express
 - o **dreamStream** Deployed Site: <u>dreamStream</u> Repository: <u>GitHub</u>
 - Built front end application display functions via Handlebars.js and Bootstrap and used MySQL for SQL server connection.
 - Designed the front end of the site including artwork and branding.
 - Key Tools: MySQL, Handlebars.js, Bootstrap
 - o Where ISS It? Deployed Site: Where ISS It? Repository: GitHub
 - Employed the <u>Where the ISS at?</u> API to track the location of the ISS and compare it with the location of the user.
 - Built the front end of the application and oversaw design choices.
 - Key Tools: Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH CAROLINA & CHINESE UNIVERSITY OF HONG KONG JOINT PROGRAM - INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS AND CHINESE ENTERPRISE

Bachelor of Science – Dual Major: International Business & Economics, Minor: Chinese Language

MARCELO ANDRES PEREZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Professional Experience

TARGET, RECEIVER - Denver, CO 2021-2023

- Responsible for receiving the general merchandise daily trailer.
- Perform weekly inventory audits for the whole store.
- Complete three weekly orders to stock the fresh market.
- Manage all shipments of ESIM, store to store transfers, and inventory removals.

RE/MAX PROFESSIONALS, CLIENT CARE COORDINATOR - Denver, CO 2020

- Created marketing material for single family homes using InDesign & Photoshop.
- Managed multiple social media pages.
- Organized community events such as Food Drives & Community outreach.
- Managed the schedule of two agents and the paperwork for home closings.

JAMES CAPITAL ADVISORS, MARKETING ASSOCIATE – Los Angeles, CA 2019 – 2020 (moved agencies with partners from Marcus & Millichap)

- Created marketing material for multifamily & net lease listings for 50+ agents using InDesign & Photoshop.
- Worked with agents to understand each listing's selling points to best market the property.
- Edited photos through the use of Photoshop, Lightroom, & Luminar.
- Created site plans for listings through the use of Photoshop.
- Created & scheduled email blasts for clients through the use of Pardot & Salesforce.

MARCUS & MILLICHAP, MARKETING & CLIENT SERVICES ASSISTANT - Los Angeles, CA 2018 - 2019

- Created marketing material for 6 agents through the use of Adobe InDesign & Photoshop.
- Sourced rent & sales comparables & helped underwrite multifamily apartment buildings
- Created & scheduled email blasts for clients through the use of Constant Contact.
- Prepared physical BOVs for meetings with clients.

KNIGHT FRANK, JUNIOR LETTINGS NEGOTIATOR, ALDGATE OFFICE – London, UK 2016 – 2017 (two multi-month contracts)

- Showed properties to prospective renters in East London.
- Increased profits by executing an average of 15 lettings monthly.
- Acted as executive assistant for 2-3 Lettings Managers/Negotiators daily.
- Managed administrative tasks including scheduling and data entry.
- Conducted professional phone and desk reception.